carmike.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy

#### **Privacy Policy**

Carmike Cinemas, Inc. has designed this policy to maximize your ability to protect your personal information, while at the same time enabling us to provide you the opportunity to obtain interesting and useful information, products and services. At no time are you obligated to provide us any personal information, and if at any time you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you are free to "opt out" of receiving these communications. Because this Privacy Policy applies to any person who provides information through a Carmike Cinemas web site, we recommend that you to review this Privacy Policy in its entirety. By using this web site, you accept this Privacy Policy and any other applicable terms. 

**Our use of your personal information** We collect information through our web site to enhance the experience of visitors to our site. We (including our affiliates) may use this information in a number of ways. This information is collected to furnish you with products or services you have requested, or to send you information or otherwise contact you about Carmike Cinemas, or its affiliates, our products, services, advertising, upcoming events, special offers or promotions, or for other purposes disclosed when you submit your information to our web site; to assist us in marketing and advertising our products and services and those of other businesses; to improve the content and navigation on our web site; to prevent and detect fraud, infringement, and other potential misuse of our web site. We do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure - by opting in to receive information from a third party that is participating in a sweepstakes or other promotion on one of our web sites. If you do not want your information to be used by a third party for direct marketing purposes (or other purposes unrelated to the uses described herein), do not opt in to such use by that third party. Please note that if you opt in to receive direct marketing from a third party, your information will be subject to that party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact that third party directly. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

**Opt-Out - To remove your name and information from our lists** You have the choice to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us, and to limit our disclosure of your information to other companies. You can also change or modify information previously provided. You may opt out on the “My Account” tab or by e-mailing our customer service department at rewardcards@Carmike.com.

**Children Guidelines** Carmike does not specifically target its online services to children under 13 years old. If you are under the age of 13 you may use our web site only under the supervision of a parent or guardian. Please note that our site may contain links to content providers that collect information from children under the age of 13. We have no control over such content providers and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites. Because the Internet offers open access to a wide range of information, it is important that parents supervise and prevent access to inappropriate content, email or chat sessions.

**Cookies** Our Web sites collect information through a variety of technical methods, including cookies and Web beacons. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the Web site. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of Web sites. Cookies, web beacons and other technical methods may involve the transmission of information directly to us.

**Security** The personal information collected by Carmike Cinemas is stored in limited access servers, accessible only by Carmike employees. We will maintain appropriate safeguards, including technical measures, warnings, and firewalls, to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of any customer information under our control. Please be aware that the transmission of information over the Internet is not inherently secure, and, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security measures, no security systems can prevent all potential security breaches.

**Disclosure Required by Law.** From time to time, Carmike may be required to share your personally identifiable information with law enforcement or other governmental agencies in response to a court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. Carmike also reserves the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that Carmike Cinemas, in good faith, believes to be unlawful. Carmike also may share certain personally identifiable information when it believes that such sharing is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and itself.

**Policy Modifications** Carmike may change the terms of this Privacy Policy periodically. Any changes made will be posted immediately to the Privacy Policy section within this site. Your continued use of our site after any change has been posted constitutes acceptance of the change to this Privacy Policy.

V 1.2 (Revision Date: May 2015)
